{
    "subject": "resource/Hannibal_(film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Hannibal_Lecter",
    "human_readable": "The film Hannibal is about Hannibal Lecter.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9570462703704834,
            "question": "What film is Hannibal Lecter featured in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8955950736999512,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'Hannibal'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8154857754707336,
            "question": "Is Hannibal Lecter a real person?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.809439480304718,
            "question": "Who is the main character in the film 'Hannibal'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7947638630867004,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'Hannibal'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7659868597984314,
            "question": "What are some themes explored in the film 'Hannibal'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7652069330215454,
            "question": "What makes Hannibal Lecter a compelling character?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.633368730545044,
            "question": "What are some common characteristics associated with Hannibal Lecter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.603227972984314,
            "question": "Are there any sequels or prequels to the film 'Hannibal'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5792694091796875,
            "question": "What is the overall tone of the film 'Hannibal'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The film Hannibal is about Hannibal Lecter.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5825_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any sequels or prequels to the film 'Hannibal'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5825_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common characteristics associated with Hannibal Lecter?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5825_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes Hannibal Lecter a compelling character?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5825_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5825_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5825_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5825_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5825_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5825_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5825_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5825_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5825_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5825_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5825_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the movie \"Hannibal,\" which indeed revolves around Hannibal Lecter. This supports the statement that the film \"Hannibal\" is about Hannibal Lecter."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}